on the territory of modern Ukraine and
на территории современной Украины и
Belarus lived Slavic tribes uh
Белоруси жили славянские племена ээ
Polyane Drevlyane Ulichi Tivertsi uh Krivichi
поляне древляне уличи тиверцы ээ кривичи
there and so on Vyati and what Slavic
там и так дальше вяти а какое славянское
tribe lived on the territory of the city of Vladimir
племя жило на территории города Владимир
Moscow Suzdal on these territories
Москва Суздаль на этих территориях
Dagestanis
дагестанцы
look at the Ukrainian flag
посмотри украинский флаг
normally let's talk today is Victory Day come on come on
нормально поговорим сегодня день победы
normally Victory Day and
давай давай нормально день победы а
today is Victory Day
сегодня же день победы сегодня день
today is Victory Day today is Victory Day yes come on
победы сегодня день победы да давай
normally yes can you name some
нормально да можете назвать каких-то
heroes of the Soviet Union of the Soviet Union
героев Советского Союза советского Союза
heroes of the Soviet Union my grandfather
героев Советского Союза дед мой
no well some no not
не ну каких-то
exactly heroes the title of Heroes of the
не не именно героев звание героев
Soviet Union just didn't come to my grandfather
Советского Союза просто так деду не
General Zhukov comrade Stalin question I
генерал Жуков товарищ Сталин вопрос я
see I'm doing a survey or do Russians
смотрю делаю опрос или россияне
uh remember because I studied I
ээ помнят потому что я учил ещё я в
studied in a Soviet school yes uh Heroes of the
советской школе учился да ээ Героев
Soviet Union look I'll show you a
Советского Союза смотри я сейчас покажу
photo now and you say is this Zhukov
фотографию а вы скажите это Жуков
Tukhachevsky or Kosior or Kosior this is
Тухачевский или Косиор или косиор
this and you're normal this is Zhukov
вот это а ты норма вот это Жуков
Tukachevsky or Kosol or Korov look
Тукачевский или Косол или Коров смотри
this is this in any case no no  Zhukov because
это это по-любому не не Жуков потому что
it is not Zhukov oh right because
это не Жуков о правильно потому что
Zhukov Zhukov
Жуков Жуков
switched off Tukhachevsky or Kos ko
отключился тухачевский или Кос ко
wait quietly
подожди тихо
svera koshe
свера коше
wait 5 seconds this come on
подожди 5 секунд это давай ещё раз
show me again Zhukov Tukhachevsky or koser Zhukov
покажи жуков Тухачевский или косёр жуков
Tukhachevsky or
Тухачевский или
this is
это
Nuni Zhukovska Tukhachevsky or Kova not
Нуни Жуковска Тухачевский или Кова не
Zhukov left Tukhachev and Kosi
жуков осталось тухачев и коси
and this is in
а это
any case well show me again and you in
по-любому а ну ещё раз покажи а ты
short you are looking for like which of them I understand
короче ты ищешь типа кто из них я понял
you are now in short you are looking for like which of them I understand
ты сейчас короче ты ищешь типа кто из
you are now googling no I am not
них я понял ты сейчас гуглишь нет я не
googling this is in any case some kosior
гуглю это по-любому косиор какой-нибудь
yes right come on handsome
да правильно давай красава
right now you guessed the second one correctly
правильно сейчас второго правильно
I am a good boy now I will give the second one well
угадал я молодец сейчас второго дам ну
damn usually I don't know
блин обычно не знаю
usually I don't know
обычно не знаю
because we are citizens of Russia
потому что мы громадяне России
well I understand yes yes and where are we from well I understand
ну я понимаю да да а сами откуда ну я
yes yes and where are we
понимаю да ну да а сами откуда
from Crimea well that is deception understood understood go or
с Крым ну то есть обманда понял
something now wait we can't do
понял гони что ли сейчас подожди у нас
anything he doesn't have anything like
ничего у него не получается
that now
не было же такого
now now sound now  sound
сейчас сечас сейчас звук сечасчас звук
yes come on go there talk and
да давай иди туда заговаривай а
I asked: "And what are you doing what kind of stream
я спросил: "А ты что ведёшь какой стрим
or not stream I just
или не стрим я просто
choose watch or Russians remember
выбираю смотрю или россияне помнят
heroes
героев
come on what what what come on come on from the heroes of the
давай что что что давай давай из героев
Great Patriotic War who is this uh
Великой Отечественной войны кто это ээ
Kotovsky or Shcher Kotovsky or I
Котовский или Щёр котовский или
didn't
не
understand Kotovsky or
понял котовский или
Shcherz no wait
щёрз нет подожди
you're smart
ты умный
beautiful wait wait wait who is this
красивая подожди подожди подожди кто это
show normally
покажи нормально
no yes this is [ __ ] this is now the
не да это шёрт
third we'll try now the
этость сейчас третий попробуем сейчас
third we'll try come on let's try
третий попробуем давай давай попробуем
you we ours
ты мы своих
No well
Не ну
really
реально
hear what you recognize recognize and wait he
слышати что узнаёте узнаёте а подожди он
wants to knock us down understood like we I want to
нас хочет завалить понял типа мы Я хочу
knock down but I'm now something
завалить но я сейчас сложное что-то Я
complicated I'll give something complicated now come on come on come on come on so
сейчас сложное что-то дам ну давай давай
you're beautiful well
давай давай так ты красивая
yes I know I talked to you
ну да вот я знаю я с тобой разговаривал
this is Kolk or Wrangel Kolchak or
это Колк или Врангель колчак или
Wrangel banazh I didn't understand understood Kolchak or
Врангель банаж не понял понял колчак или
Wrangel or Wrangel SS normally the USSR is
Врангель или Врангель сс нормально СССР
not visible there from this on  I'm still
там не видно ни там от это на меня всё
throwing off
скидывает
this I say you know what Korczak or in the rank of
это говорю знаешь что корчак или в ранге
Korczak or in the rank of don't wait
корчак или в ранге не подожди ещё раз
tell me again look who is this from the heroes of the USSR from the
скажи смотри кто это из героев ССС из
heroes of the USSR Kolchak or Wrangel Kolchak or
героев СССР колчак или Врангель колчак
Wrangel you are an
Врангель ты это
Iliger
илигер
and I thought you Come on Kolchak or Wrangel
а я думал ты Давай колчак или Врангель
Kolchak or Wrangel
колчак или Врангель
this is Wrangel Wrangel yes some
это Врангель врангель да какие-то
some
какие-то
how did the soldiers take you if you know all this
как вас солдаты взяли если вы шарите это
you studied to be a historian
ты на историка учился
because in Russia there are smart soldiers too got it got it guys
потому что в России умные солдаты тоже
okay in short they
есть понял понял пацаны ладно короче это
were Stepan Bandera Roman Shukhevych and
были Степан Бандера Роман Шухевич и
Yevhen Konovach glory to Ukraine
Евген Коновач слава Украине
[laughter]
[смех]
hi hello I'm from the city of
привет здравствуйте я из города
Khmelnitsky and where are you from
Хмельницкий а ты откуда
I'm from Nizhny Novgorod it's cool my
я с Нижнего Новгорода прикольно у меня
father is from Arzamas and what do you communicate
из Арзамаса отец родом а чем общаешься
here yes I just talk with interesting
тут да просто разговариваю с интересными
people
людьми
cool interesting topic about which well
прикольно интересная тема на какие
about different cities I communicate let's
ну про города разные общаюсь давай
talk about history about Bakhmut why did
историю пообщаемся о Бахмуте зачем
Russia destroy it I
Россия уничтожила его
don't know
не знаю
and what cities are you  you communicate
а какие городах ты общаешься
Moscow Vladimir Golden Ring of Russia
москва Владимир Золотое кольцо России
come on Moscow Vladimir Golden Ring of
давай москва Владимир Золотое кольцо
Russia in what year was Vladimir founded
России в каком году был основан Владимир
Moscow Moscow
москва
was founded in 1147 I
москва была основана в 1147 году я про
asked about Moscow oh about Vladimir I asked
Москву спроси ой про Владимир спросил
again what did you ask when
ещё раз про что вы спросили когда был
Vladimir was founded
основан Владимир
882 oh 982 by
882 ой 982 год
whom was Vladimir founded
кем был основан Владимир
Vladimir Manomakh Manomakh Manomakh lived
владимир Маномахом маномахом маномах жил
in 982 no of course Manomakh did not live in
в 982 нет конечно Маномах не жил в 982
982 you when was Vladimir founded
году ты когда был основан Владимир
in 91 what in 91
в 91 году что в 91 году
990 that was still Prince Vladimir he baptized Rus in 988
990 это ещё князь Владимир был он в 988
after him was Yaroslav the Wise yes and then
после него был Ярослав Мудрый да а потом
somewhere there this mono well in 118 it
уже где-то там этот моно хорошо в 118
was with
году было с
B8
В8
yes look now the time of life of
да вот посмотри вот сейчас время жизни
Vladimir Manomakh years he lived a long time ago
Владимира Маномаха года он давно жил уже
now of course he does not live
сейчас конечно не живёт
look you
посмотри
know the capital of the Czech Republic Prague
знаете столицу Чехии прага
and Warsaw
а Варшава
Poland and Estonia Estonia Latvia Bratislava
польша а Эстония эстония латвия
la  estonia talin talin yes
братислав ла эстония талин талин да
why well because you have not guessed already
почему ну потому что ты уже не отгадал
look monomakh monomakh was born in
вот смотри мономах мономах родился в
1053 only
1053 году только
in 1153 in 1053 well when was the baptism of
в 1153 в 1053 хорошо когда было крещение
Rus
Руси
988 then when Kyiv was founded then you are
988 то когда Киев был основан то ты
running away from when Vladimir was founded
убегаешь от того когда был основан
then how could you watch it 1108 well no not
то как его мог смотреть 1108 ну нет не
Manomakh well I just said no then
Маномах хорошо я просто сказал нет то
if 1.108 already fits Monomakh well
если 1.108 уже подходит под Мономаха ну
1.125 somewhere else so now tell me
1.125 где-то оста так теперь расскажи
which ones that's very simple eh cool question
какие вот очень просто э классный вопрос
if you are an expert on the golden ring of
если ты специалист по золотому кольцу
Russia here
России вот
in the namerv of Ukraine and Belarus lived
намерв Украины и Беларуси жили
Slavic
славянские
tribes Polyane Drevlyane Ulichi Tivertsi
племена поляне древляне уличи
Krivichi there and so on Vyati and
тиверцы кривичи там и так дальше вяти а
what Slavic tribe lived on the
какое славянское племя жило на
territory of the city of Vladimir Moscow
территории города Владимир Москва
Suzdal on these territories
Суздаль на этих территориях
Ukrainians no there was no such tribe well
украинцы нет не было такого племени ну
look there was no tell me if Slavs lived there
вот смотри не было скажи если там жили
what do you think who lived on
славяне ты как считаешь там кто жили на
these territories  Slavs or not Slavs
этих территориях славяне или не славяне
Slavs if Slavs what was the name of the
славяне вот если славяне как называлось
Slavic tribe that lived in
славянское племя которое проживало на
those
тех
territories Dagestanis
территориях дагестанцы
you see you don't know this is your history
видишь ты ж не знаешь это твоя история
well I forgot a little after all there were no
ну чуть-чуть подзабыл всё-таки не было
Slavs in those territories
на этих территориях славян там жили
Finno-Ugric peoples lived there including the tribes of
финоугорские народы в том числе племена
Merya Murom Erzya
Меря Мурома Эрзя
that is on the Vladimir land Finugorsk
то есть на Владимирской земле Финугорске
yes Finu-Ugric lands yes and then the
да Финуугорские земли да а тогда
Khazar Khaganate where the Khazar
Хазардский каганат где был хазарский
Khaganate was was where Astrakhan is that's where yeah the
каганат был там где Астрахань вот там
capital was Sarkel on the Don and Itil on the
столица была Саркел на Дону и Итиль на
Volga also Prince Svyatoslav Khorobriy
Волге ещё ж князь Святослав Хоробрий
of Kiev defeated the capital of the Khazar
Киевский разбил столицу Хазарского
Khaganate
каганата
okay then explain to me let's see it turns out it's
хорошо то объясни мне давай получается
interesting lived there lived there that's where
вот интересно жили там жили там вот где
you have the Golden Ring of Russia lived
у вас Золотое кольцо России жили
Finno-Ugric tribes Merya and so on
финоугорские племена Меря и так дальше
yes
да
Slavic Slavic tribes did not
славянские славянские племена там не
live there yes that's the question
жили да то вопрос
No they did not live yes the question is the people who
Нет не жили да вопрос то люди которые
live there in those territories are the
живут там на этих территориях это
heirs of the Slavs or  heirs of the Finno
наследники славян или наследники
-Ugric tribes heirs of the
финоугорских племён наследники
Finno-Ugric tribes it turns out that the
финугорских племён получается вот то
Russians are essentially these
есть русские - это по сути и есть эти
Finno-Ugric tribes that were Slavized by the
финогорские племена которым ославянили
language of which Well, it turns out that I understood it
языком которых Ну выходишь что так понял
super what other cities are you interested in
супер какие ещё города тебя интересуют
Achinsk
ачинск
Achinsk Achinsk is where you don't know no
ачинск ачинск - это где вы не знаете нет
in Russia where is Arzamas
в России где Арзамас
maybe
может быть
maybe not
может и нет
and what's interesting there in Achinsk in Achinsk there
и что там интересно в Ачинске в Ачинске
used to live super who are you by
там узбеки раньше жили супер ты кто по
nationality
национальности вообще
Russian doesn't look like a Russian who do you
русский не похож на русский на кого
look like an Uzbek wait and what city are you from
похож на узбека подожди а ты из какого
Arzamas
арзамаз
where are you Russian are you Erzya no it's an
откуда ты русский ты Эрзя
Erzya city Erzyamas it was
нет это ж Эрзянский город эрзямас он был
no why is it a Russian city
нет почему это русский город там никогда
Russians have never lived
русские отродяси не жили
there maybe in the Novgorod
может быть там в нов в Новгородской
region Tatars lived Chuvash lived
области жили татары жили чуваши жили
Morians lived and Erzya lived that's just Ar
морийцы и жили Эрзя вот как раз Ар
Arzamas is one of the northern cities of the
Арзамас - это один из северных городов
land of Arzy
земли Арзы
ok and tell me what the colors of
хорошо а расскажите что означают цвета
your flag mean
вашего флага
m the
м
colors of your flag mean nothing
цвета вашего флага ничего не означает
ok and tell us the origin of your
хорошо а расскажите происхождение вашего
coat of arms
герба
what coat of arms exactly do you have on your
какого именно герба у которого у вас на
chest tell us what coat of arms we have who
груди расскажи какой у нас герб
invented it tell us who has what kind of
кто его придумал вам расскажи кто у Что
sign tell us what it's called
это за знак расскажи как называется
know its sign well tell me what it's called I
знать его зна ну назови как называется я
just don't know what you're talking about trident
просто не знаю о чём ты тризубец
trident yes oh right why is it
тризубец да о правильно почему он
called trident well
называется тризубец
I've kind of forgotten its history already
ну я что-то подзабыл уже его историю ну
think about the word trident why three teeth
подумай слово тризубец почему три зуба
because that's right super and why does
потому что правильно супер а почему у
it have three teeth
него три зуба
the rest were knocked out
остальные выбили
because look when Prince Vladimir came
потому что смотри когда князь Владимир
up with it well you know that Prince
себе придумал ну вы знаете что князь
Vladimir basically created it no he didn't
Владимир в принципе его создал нет не
create it and Prince Vladimir had it before
создал он и до него был у князя
it was a princely sign it
Владимира это был княжеский знак он
meant that
означал что
when in the northern swamps he comes up with a coat of arms the
когда на северных болотах придумает герб
Chernobyl two-headed chicken yes then
чернобыльскую двухглавую курицу да то
these will be the pitchforks on which it will be
это будут те вила на которые её
impaled and you're just a dummy and I called you names
наколят а ты дол просто а я вас обзывал
no but I called you names and that's somehow incorrect
нет а я обозвал и что ну некорректно
you don't agree
ты не соглашусь
you're okay it's a
ты
pity hmm it
о'кей жаль хм
was funny yes not a bad thing yes very funny
смешно было да некоре да смешно очень
funny let's
смешно давай
go I didn't
идём я не
insult joke about Ukraine in short for
оскорблял шутить про Украину короче для
him it's normal
него норм
yes and here Opa
да а тут Опа
hello to you heart
привет тебе сердеч
oh thank you I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky and where are you
о спасибо я из города Хмельницкий а ты
from oh Bohdan Khmelnitsky is the
откуда ой Богдан Хмельницкий это же
famous Hetman of Ukraine oh you have a
Гетман знаменитый украин ой у тебя тут
cool badge here well
значок прикольный а ну
show me and that's the sun and the moon there month yes well that was
покажи а это там солнце и луна месяц да
18 years old yes and now how much
ну это 18 лет было да а сейчас сколько
23 got it I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky and where are you
23 понял я из города Хмельницкий а ты
from Moscow and where did you come to Moscow from
откуда москвы а в Москву откуда приехала
scologs
скологи
got it what are you
понял о чём тут
talking about here somehow just about this and that
общаешься как-то просто вот о том о сём
somehow no specifically about and what do you work as a
как-то нет конкретно о а кем работаешь
teacher of what
учителем чего
history damn colleagues I'm a teacher at the
истории блин коллеги я преподаватель в
university of history oh it turns
университете истории
out yes yes 18 years of practice in
о получается да да 18 лет практики через
2 years you will already be
2 года будет уже
twenty you probably have a smaller
двадцаточка у тебя наверное поменьше
anniversary further yes I'm far from me of
дальше юбилей да мне до меня далеко до
course that's interesting yes if you are from
конечно вот интересно да если ты из
history a history teacher can say
истори учитель истории можешь сказать
so uh there was Kievan Rus there was not
так ээ вот была Киевская Русь
again there was not
ещё раз не было
so explain to me
так объясни мне
the concept of Kievan Rus invented now
понятие Киевской Руси придумано сейчас
in order to understand the state yes it
для того чтобы понять государство да оно
was called Rus everything is correct not in  in
называлось Русь всё правильно не в
the twentieth and in the nineteenth yes that is well there
двадцатом а в девятнадцатом да то есть
was a state of Rus with the center in
ну вот было государство Русь с центром в
Kyiv so so
Киеве так
so there were no other Ruses
так так никаких других Русей больше не
really really really the question uh
было правда правда правда вопрос ээ
what relation does Russia the Muscovite
какое отношение Россия московское
state yes have to Rus
государство да имеет к Руси
well the question is where did they come from to
хорошо вопрос в том откуда пришли чтобы
unite Kyiv where from with what with what
объединить Киев откуда с чем с каким
city from Novgorod so firstly let's
городом с Новгорода так во-первых давай
what relation does Ukraine have to
на какое отношение Украина имеет к
Novgorod when the question let's look
Новгороду когда вопрос давай смотри
first the Muscovite state captured
первый московское государство захватила
Novgorod in what century
Новгород в каком веке
Novgorod was not captured in the fifteenth
новгород не захватывали в пятнадцатом
there yes here second from nowhere from Novgorod did
там да вот второе ниоткуда из Новгорода
not come to Kyiv pon and is called
не приходили в Киев пон и называется
Novgorod why a
Новгород почему
new city a new city that is if there was a
новый город новый город то есть если был
New City then there were old cities
Новый город значит были старые города
really it is clearly not older than Kyiv really
правда он явно не старше Киева правда
so Ladoga city Ladoga cities there
так Ладога города ладога города там
were never really that is the
никогда не было правда
first capital of Rus does not
то есть первая столица Руси вас не
confuse you Ladogan was never the
смущает ладоган никогда не было ни
capital of Rus or the first capital of Rus
столицей Руси ни первой столицей Руси
well let's say okay so can you
хорошо допустим ладно так мо можешь мне
tell me where it was written that Ladoga
сказать где было написано что Ладога
was the capital of Rus
была столицей Руси
and where it is not written no it was invented
а где это не написано нет это придумали
in the 19th century  just when it was necessary to
в XIX веке как раз да когда нужно было
stretch an owl on a globe
натягивать сову на глобус
so well well where well you as a historian
так хорошо ну где ну ты как историк
tell me where it is written that Ladoga was the
скажи где написано что Ладога была
capital of Rus' well it was not well
столица Руси хорошо не была хорошо
let's say okay I understood in what year
допустим ладно понял в каком году
Novgorod was founded
основали Новгород
in 869 in 869 no it's not true well
в 869 в 869 нет неправда
in what year show me where the data on the
ну в каком же э покажи где данные об
foundation of the city of Novgorod in 869 the
основании города Новгород в 869 году
tale of bygone years open the tale of
повесть временных лет открыть повесть
bygone years in what century it was written
временных лет в каком столетии писалась
12 here 300 years after these events
12 вот через 300 лет после этих событий
the Tale of Bygone Years as you know this is
повесь временных лет как ты знаешь это
not a historical document yes it
не есть исторический документ да это
is a literary work look
есть литературное произведение посмотри
where the first lines begin if you have
с чего начинается первые строки если ты
read at least once in your life the Tale of Bygone
читала хоть раз в жизни Повесь временных
Years where it begins the first
лет с чего она начинается первое
sentence the first phrase
предложение первая фраза
we seem to be talking about this not about this
мы кажется не об этом говорим не об этом
about this it says there yes that after the
об этом об этом там сказано да что после
flood uh the children of Noah went there in short there and there and
потопа ээ дети Ноя пошли там короче туда
there there sima hama ifet that is to say
туда и туда там сима хама ифет вот то
this is not a historical source
есть это не исторический источник
it was written 300 years after the
писался он в через 300 лет после тех
events to which it seems to
событий на которые он вроде как
refer yes naturally there are
ссылается да вот естественно там даты
absolutely no dates  coincide with
абсолютно не совпадают с
reality, that is, historians, yes,
действительностью то есть историками да
nowhere in other documents, neither in
нигде ни в других документах ни в
German nor in Swedish, nowhere is there that there
германских ни в шведских нигде нету что
was some Novgorod, yes, in the century,
там был какой-то Новгород да в веке
archeology, yes, in Novgorod, does not show
археология да в Новгороде не показывает
any Slavic settlements of the century,
никакие славянские поселения века это ж
you as a historian should know this, I as a
ты как историк должна знать я как
historian know this, uh, Kyiv, yes,
историк это знаю ээ Киев да
archaeologically, can be traced back to the 5th century
археологически прослеживается с V века
without problems, yes, Slavic settlements, I do not
без проблем да славянские поселения я не
argue, so that is, Kyiv existed, and this
спорю так вот то есть Киев существовал а
knowledge comes from where, therefore, where it is
эти знания откуда что поэто где он
registered, this is archeology, this is archeology,
прописано это это археология это
look, there is even a book,
археология смотри вот есть даже книжка
for example, Slavs on Slavs in Podolia,
например славяны на славяне на Подолье
and here there is the 6th-8th century, the 6th-8th century has been
да и тут есть вот VI8 век vi-8 век
completely excavated, yes, where they
полностью раскопано да что где где
settled, oil, can you show me, yes,
селились масло можешь мне показать да
what Slavic settlements were in
какие славянские поселения были в
Novgorod in the century,
Новгороде в веке
Elmeni, what Elmeni, if you did not know that
эльмени что эльмени если вы не знали что
Elmeni, what Elmeni, Elmeni, such a tribe
Эльмени что эльмени эльмени племя такое
existed and the Slavs were not Elmeni, but Elmeni
было и славя не не эльмени а эльменские
Slaveni were called, so in
славени назывались так вот в самом
Novgorod itself, show me  yes what were the
Новгороде покажи мне да какие были
Slavic settlements yes what were the
славянские городища да какие были в
Slavic settlements on this territory in the
славянские городища на этой территории в
century listen the person who says
веке слушайте человек который говорит
that Kievan Rus was at the same time
что Киевская Русь была в один момент с
when Novgorod was captured can no longer be
тем когда захватывали Новгород уже не
read by a historian what hello hello
может читаться историком какой алло алло
where did you run off to fried this historian that's how the
ты куда убежала прожарили эту историчку
palms shmadagi in short damn like
вот так ладоги шмадаги короче
subscribe comment subscribe
блин так лайк подписка комент підпишись
to my Telegram right now os vin and
на мій Telegram прямо зараз ось він а
pop this is very and very important youtube
попик це дуже і дуже важливо youtube
drives us through cards into a shadow ban and
заганяе нас через карки в тіньовий бан и
very many videos are not shown to people
дуже багато відео не показуется людям
at times information about
вчасно не показуется інформація про
streams is not shown so that we have a small
стрими тому для того щоб ми мали
operational link subscribe right
оперативный зв'язок підпишиться прямо
now and pop there is an okmdeo in telegram
зараз а попик там в телеграмі окмдео ще
also interesting and  useful information and we are
теж є цікава и корисна інформація и мы
obliged to maintain constant
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational communication with you regardless of what
оперативный зв'язок незалежно від того
YouTube will show you about this glory of
чи покаже вам про цей YouTube слава
Ukraine subscribe
Україні підпишись